Jamieson Reinhard

jamieson.reinhard2@gmail.com // linkedin.com/in/jamiesonreinhard

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY:



Versatile full-stack software developer with experience creating and maintaining responsive production web applications. Has worked across several stacks, sometimes developing multiple projects simultaneously. Versed in startups and helping product owners turn ideas into highly functional POC's. Experience managing and mentoring other developers, as well as years of additional experience in finance and accounting.

FRONTEND / UIUX SKILLS:

- HTML5

- Next.js

- CSS3

- Typescript

- Javascript ES6

- Figma, Adobe XD

- React.js

- TailwindCSS

BACKEND / DATABASE SKILLS:

- Python

- AWS DynamoDB

- Ruby on Rails

- Web hooks

- MySQL, PostgreSQL

- Web sockets

- AWS Lambda

- API Integrations

OTHER SKILLS:

- AWS Services

- Heroku

- Bitbucket, Jira

- Netlify, Vercel

- Github

- Thunderclient

- Trello

- Postman

EDUCATION:

LE WAGON MEXICO

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp | 2020 Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, Projects.

UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO, BOULDER Bachelor of Science, Finance | 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE:

SENIOR FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER
Click Contracts | July, 2023 - November, 2023
React, Tailwind, Python, AWS Serverless, MySQL
Saas product particularly useful for real estate agents
to help manage the creation and signing of documents.

SENIOR FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Zoee | March, 2022 - July, 2023

React, Typescript, Python, AWS Lambda, MySQL

Saas product for coaches to manage their scheduling, billing, video, marketing, chat, & notes all-in-one place.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER 1

Codelation | October, 2021 - March, 2022 React, Typescript, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL Helping product owners turn ideas into outstanding products.

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER
Tempore | April, 2021 - October, 2021
JQuery, Python, AWS Lambda, MySQL

Web and mobile development of travel application.

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER
Lsat Cracked | 2020-2021
Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Heroku

Online LSAT prep course with articles, quizzes, and other learning materials.

ASSISTANT DIRECTOR OF FINANCE Marriott International & Vail Resorts | 2015 -2020